

PAOLANTONIO DIEGO GABRIEL

Córdoba, Argentina +54 9 351 754 3947 paolantonio.diego@gmail.com

LINKS

<u>LINKEDIN</u> <u>PORFOLIO</u>

SKILLS

HTML
CSS
BOOTSTRAP
SASS
JavaScript
React JS
Node JS
GitHub
FrontEnd Development

LANGUAGES

Spanish – Native English – Intermediate Portuguese – Intermediate

ABOUT ME

I am electronic engineer, I studied at Universidad Tecnológica Nacional FRC, with extensive experience in industrial automation, I am making a job change, I always liked programming, which is why I am training as a Full Stack Developer, my goal is be able towork as a developer and continue training in its different branches.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer
June 2022 - Present
Electronic Engineer / Automatist

Responsibilities: Technical assistance \cdot PLC Programming \cdot Electrical design \cdot Project management \cdot Technical management \cdot Team management \cdot Process automation.

CORAUTOMATICA SRL May 2014 – May 2022

Partner / Electronic Engineer / Automatist.

 $\textbf{Responsibilities} : \textbf{Technical assistance} \cdot \textbf{PLC Programming} \cdot \textbf{Electrical design} \cdot \textbf{Project} \\ \textbf{management} \cdot \textbf{Technical management} \cdot \textbf{Team management} \cdot \textbf{Process automation}.$

BETONMAC Jule 2013 – May 2014 Developer

Responsibilities: Automatic systems Develoment for the production of concrete. Printed Circuit Board Design (PCB), PLC programming, C/C++ programming ofAtMega microcontrollers

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CODERHOUSE, Argentina Jule 2022 - Present

- .. - . . - . . - . . -

Full Stack Developer Career includes:

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, Flexbox, Grid, SASS, BOOTSTRAP, Github.
- JavaScript: JavaScript, DOM, JSON, Node JS, File System.
- React JS: React JS, API's, Firebase.
- BackEnd Programming: JavaScript, File System, MongoDB, Mongoose, express, passport y otros.

ELECTRONIC ENGINEER

UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA NACIONAL FRC, Córdoba, Argentina 2004 - 2015